Guide to the Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection, circa 1976-2009 MS2040
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection
circa 1976-2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Peabody, Richard M.
MS2040
84 Linear Feet
Collection contains material accumulated and generated by Richard Peabody, specifically during his tenure as founder, editor and publisher of Paycock Press. The collection primarily consists of reference material, such as community arts promotional literature and literary publications, in which some of Peabody's work appears and which he used as source material for his book.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
In 1990, Richard Peabody donated a collection of community arts promotional literature to George Washington University's Gelman Library. The literature promoted cultural events in the Washington, DC area during the years ca. 1976 and 1992. Three years later, the library purchased the Richard M. Peabody Gargolye Magazine Collection, which was added to his previous donation. Peabody retained all literary property and copyright ownership of the material.
Series 6 Gift of Richard Peabody, 02/18/2010 (Accession 2010.006).
Historical or Biographical Note
Richard Myers Peabody, Jr. (1951- ) is a life long resident of the Washington DC area and has been a central figure in the literary intellectual life of the city. Peabody was one of the founding editors and publisher of Gargoyle magazine, a highly regarded Washington DC literary journal that published 36 issues between 1976 and 1990. Gargoyle magazine, which Peabody funded almost completely with his modest personal income, published the work of local writers as well as the literary compositions of internationally known authors, such as T.C. Boyle and Charles Bukowski. Peabody also ran an independent publishing company, Paycock Press, for which he designed, edited and published twelve books from 1976 to 1990.
Peabody is the author of three books of poetry, Sad Fashions (1990), Echt & Ersatz (1985), and I'm in Love with the Morton Salt Girl (1979), as well as a volume of short fiction entitled Monaural (1980). He has also edited several collections, including D.C. Magazines: A Literary Perspective (1982), Mavericks: Nine Independent Publishers (1983), Mondo Barbie (1993) and Coming to Terms: A Literary History of Abortion (1994). He has published numerous poems and fictional articles in Here!, Unicorn Times, Carousel, Trouser Press, The American Magazine, New South Writing, as well as many others.
A Washington, DC native, Peabody earned his degrees from local universities a bachelor of arts in English from the University of Maryland in 1973 and a masters in Art Literature from The American University in 1975. He attended Georgetown Writer's Conference in the summer of 1975. Peabody has taught creative writing courses and workshops at St. John's College in Annapolis, Maryland, at The Writer's Center in Bethesda, Maryland, at Georgetown University and at the University of Maryland.
Gelman Library retains an extensive collection of Peabody's Gargoyle magazine, as well as the book, D.C. Magazines: A Literary Retrospective, which he edited in 1981. The Peabody Gargoyle Magazine Collection is part of the Washington Writers Archives (WWA) at the Gelman Library's Department of Special Collections. WWA includes original manuscripts and records from writer's organizations in the Washington, DC area. Other collections in this archive include The David McAleavey Papers, which contains videotaped footage of Peabody speaking at the Washington Writing Conference, The Grace Cavalieri Papers, The Poetry Committee of the Greater Washington Area Records and The Word Works Records.
Gargoyle Magazine was an American anthology including poetry, fiction, articles, art, photos, interviews, satire, reviews, long poems, parts of novels and collages of European and American writers and artists. The magazine was founded in Bethesda, Maryland in 1976 by Richard Peabody, Russell Cox and Paul Pasquarella. Thirty eight issues were published between 1976 and 1990. Contributors were paid with one copy of the magazine in which their work appeared. The magazine is indexed in the Index of American Periodical Verse. In 1979, Peabody's independent publishing company, Paycock Press, began publishing books.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains material accumulated and generated by Richard Peabody, specifically during his tenure as founder, editor and publisher of Paycock Press (1976-1990). The collection primarily consists of reference material, such as community arts promotional literature and literary publications, in which some of Peabody's work appears and which he used as source material for his book.
Also included in the collection is correspondence from contributing Gargoyle authors and artists and general correspondence from writers, who submitted their work for consideration in the publication. Graphics, negatives and page mechanicals document the production of Gargoyle and other Paycock Press publications, Administrative material generated in the course of business is included, as well.
This collection is a valuable historical record of the publication process of a major literary magazine in the Washington DC area and is an excellent resource for information on literary organizations and cultural institutions during the 1970s and 1980s.
The collection measures approximately 84 linear feet. Material in the collection dates from ca. 1970 to 1992 and exemplifies Peabody's intimate familiarity with the Washington metro area.
This collection is part of the Washington Writers Archives at Gelman Special Collections, which includes original manuscripts and records from writers's organizations in the Washington D.C. area.
Collection Organization
Organized into six series: Publications, Correspondence, Reference files, Productions files, Administrative files, and Flyers and brochures.
Literature; Washington (D.C.); Fiction -- Washington (D.C.); Gargoyle Magazine; Bukowski, Charles; Peabody, Richard M.
- Publications, 1981-2002; MS2040 Series 1
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of copies of issues published by Paycock Press, including a copy of DC Magazine: A Literary Retrospective (1982), issues of Gargoyle Magazine and audio recordings of both Gargoyle and other publications.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 15/16, 1980; Series 1 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 17/18, 1981; Series 1 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Paycock Press Publications, D.C. Magazines: A Literary Retrospective, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    General note
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle #19, 1982; Series 1 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 24, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 25/26, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 27, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Fiction/86, Gargoyle 30/31, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 32/33, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 35, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 37/38, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 37/38, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 41, 1998; Series 1 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 42, 1999; Series 1 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Paycock Press Publications, Gargoyle 44, 2002; Series 1 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Museum of Temporary Art No. 17, Undated; Series 1 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Paycock Press publications, Gargoyle nos. 28, 29, 34, 36 [audio cassette recordings], Circa 1990-1999; Series 1 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Ten Der Hooks and untitled [audio cassette recordings], 1984; Series 1 (Box 188, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1977-1999; MS2040 Series 2
  This Series consists of correspondence saved by Peabody from 1977 to 1999. The the material includes letters, holiday cards, postcards, memos and brief notes from contributing writers of Gargoyle magazine. In some cases, the writers were Peabody's friends; therefore, the correspondence is often personal. There are also letters and notes from well known authors and artists, who submitted material or reviewed books for publication in Gargoyle.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Author Correspondence, Beth Adamour, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom Ahern, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Karren Alenier, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Elizabeth Alexander, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Frank Allen, 1981-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Henry Allen, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Roberta Allen, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Julia Alvarez, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Anbian, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Richard Anderson, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Ron Androla, 1977-1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Antler, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, David Applefield, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Bob Arnold, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Philip Athens, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Alvin Aubert, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Diana Azbell, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Ellyn Bache, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Mark Baechlet, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Eric Baizer, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Eric Baizer, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Ron Baker, n.d., undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Dierdra Baldwin, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Anna Banana, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Carolyn Banks, n.d., undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Maria Barbuto, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Lynne Barrett, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Ray Bartkowech, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Paul Bartlett, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Joe Basilone, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Mike Basinski, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Grace Bauer, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Conger Beasley, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary Beath, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, David Beaudouin, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Anne Becker, 1980-1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Les Bell, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Joe David Bellamy, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Liz Benedict, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Benedikt, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, John Bennett, 1978-1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, John M. Bennett, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Carol Berge, 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeannette Bertles, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Jim Bertolino, 1983-1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Kevin Bezner, 1982-1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence with Kevin Bezner, 1985-1989; Series 2 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Kevin Bezner, 1994-1999; Series 2 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Kevin Bezner, 1994-1999; Series 2 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, David Bianco, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary Biggs, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom Bilicke, 1979-1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom Bingham, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeanne Birdsall, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Alan Bisbort, 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Bixby, 1984-1989 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Author Correspondence, Patrick Bizzaro, 1979-1988 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Author Correspondence, Ralph Black, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Alex Blackburn, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Kate Blackwell, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Peter Blake, 1982-1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Gary Blankenburg, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Truitt Blassingham, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Norbert Blei, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Helene Bokanowski, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Bonazzi, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Paula Bonnell, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Terry Borst, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Kim S. Bowers, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Bowie, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Len Bracken, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Becky Bradway, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Katie Brady, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Jorn Bramann, 1981-1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Pamela Brandt, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeff Branin, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Susan Bright, 1982-1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Ian Brocklebank, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Anne C. Bromley, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Brondoli, 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, T.E. Brooks, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Kevin Brophy, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Chandler Brossard, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Rebecca Brown, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, James Brown, 1977-1987 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Jamie Brown, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Steven Ford Brown, 1980-1990 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Charles Brownson, 1982-1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Rickie Bruce, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Author Correspondence, Bill Buford, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Author Correspondence, Jerry Bumpus, 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Author Correspondence, Allan Burgis, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Author Correspondence, Sophy Burnham, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Author Correspondence, Jim Burns, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Author Correspondence, Peter Bushyeager, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Author Correspondence, J.D. Buttinger, n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Author Correspondence, Cairncross, George, 1977-1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Calhoun, Harry, 1983-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Carson, Anne, 1982-1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Casey, Constance, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Castle, Sandie, 1982-1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Cavalieri, Grace, 1982-1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Cervantes, Jim, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Chalkley, Tom, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Chamish, Barry, n.d., undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Chamberlin, Anne, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Cherches, Peter, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Chernoff, Maxine, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Childers, David C., 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Childers, Max, 1980-1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Choyce, Lesley, n.d., undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Ciccarelli, Rose, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Clair, Maxine, n.d., undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Claire, William F., 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Clark, Brian, C., 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Clark, Jim Wesley, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Clark, Laverne Hurrell, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Clarke, Dave, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Clearman, Mary Blew, 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Cleary, Ben C., 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Cleaves, Lisa (Forestier), 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Clift, G.W., 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Clifton, Merrit, 1980-1989 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Cline, Phil, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Clinton, DeWitt, 1984-1988 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Clinton, Michelle T., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Cochrane, Shirley Graves, 1976-1989 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Coco, Joseph, 1976-1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Author Correspondence, Cohen, Miriam A., 1982-1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Author Correspondence, Cohen, Mitch, 1984-1988 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Author Correspondence, Cole, Robert, n.d., undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Author Correspondence, Combs, Bruce, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Combs, Maxine, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Connolley, Cynthia, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Connor, Chuck, 1982-1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Cooper, Jane Todd, 1979-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Costley, Bill, 1975-1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Cotts, Cynthia, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Craver, Mark, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Creighton, Jane, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Crockett, E. Eleanor, 1982-1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Crone, Moira, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Crowell, Doug, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Cudahy, Sheila, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Currey, Richard, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Cushing, Bill, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Daitch, Susan, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Damis, James, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Daniels, Jim, n.d., undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Daniels, Kate, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Darlington, Andy, n.d., undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, D'Arpino, Tony, 1980-1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Daunt, Jon, 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Davis, Susan, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Delzell, Carmen, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Denholm, Michael, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Denison, Mike, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, DePree, Peter, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Devaul, Diane, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Devenish, Alan, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Divers, Greg, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Dixon, Stephen, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Doering, Steve, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Dorset, Gerald, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Dougherty, Jay, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Dougherty, Sean Thomas, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Dow, Jane M., 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Downer, Ann, 1983-1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Drabelle, Dennis, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Drake, Al, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Driscoll, Brian G., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Dulaner, Julia, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Duhamel, Denise, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Eady, Cornelius, 1985-1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Eakins, Patricia, 1985-1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Edmiston, Lori, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Lindsay E. Edmunds, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Egyedi, Bela, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Eidus, Janice, 1982-1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Eigner, Larry, 1971-1986 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Ellis, Normandi, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Elevitch, M.D., 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Elsberg, John, 1976-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Equi, Elaine, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Eshleman, Clayton, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Essary, Loris, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Fallenius, Charlotte, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Fallon, Joe, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Fancey, Dyane, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Fargas, Laura, n.d., undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Feeney, John, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Fericano, Paul, 1977-1983 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Findley, Jeanne, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Fischer, Carolyn, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Fisher, Harrison, 1978-1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Flanagan, Kate, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Flanagan, Richard, 1983-1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Flynn, Richard, 1982-1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Fowler, Jay, Jr., 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Fox, Bob, 1981-1986 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Fox, Hugh, 1978-1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Fox, Maryl Jo, 1978-1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Cindy Solt Frame, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Linda France, n.d., undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Marie Giblin France, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, H.E. Francis, 1983-1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Tony Frazer, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Vernon Frazer, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, James Freeman, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Freeman, Sunil, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Tina Fulker, 1978-1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Len Fulton, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Kenneth Funston, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Roger Gaess, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Forrest Gander, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Kenneth Gangemi, 1978-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Gannon, Edward, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Bill Garrison, 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Greg Gatenby, 1977-1982 (Box 10, Folder 17)